(Sheldon:)- Do you have a sword collection?
- No.
Heh, I'm not surprised.
Here's the Batman six twelve...
...with the Jim Lee aIternate cover
that you wanted.
- Oh, awesome. What do I owe you?
- Forty bucks.
- Good deal.
- Sucker.
He didn't even ask
for the friends and family discount.
I'm having a party on Friday
and I was hoping you would stop by.
- Will there be girls there?
- Of course.
Because there wasn't last time.
(Wil:)There will be girls.
(Wil:)You guys are invited
if you want to come by.
(Bernadette:)- Thank you.
- All right, great. Later.
(Sheldon:)I see what you're doing.
(Sheldon:)You accept an invitation to a party
at the home of my sworn enemy.
(Sheldon:)He tells everyone
we're going to be there.
(Sheldon:)And when we don't show,
he looks the fooI. Fiendishly clever.
(Leonard:)I was actually thinking about going.
(Sheldon:)And then declaring the party
a fiasco and storming out...
(Sheldon:)...leaving him humiliated
in front of his guests. Love it.
(Leonard:)No, I was gonna grab Raj
and Howard and have a good time.
Ah, great, more guys.
(Stuart:)It's gonna be another Wil Wheaton
sausage-fest.